valmet.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy of Valmet websites has been posted and is effective as of September 23, 2014.

The protection of your privacy during your visit to this website is very important to Valmet. Please read this Privacy Policy before using the site.

By accessing and using this site, you indicate your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy please do not use this website.

This site may contain links to other sites. Please note that Valmet is not responsible for the privacy or contents of any other websites.

In general, most of the pages on Valmet websites are provided mainly for information purposes and visitors are able to use most areas of these sites without giving any personal data. Data about your activity on Valmet websites is collected and may be connected with your personal data, if Valmet holds such data. Cookie Policy

From time to time, a small file may be placed on your computer to improve the effectiveness of this site and Valmet's services to you. This file is usually referred to as a "cookie" and many sites use this technology. Cookies are pieces of data stored on your computer's (or other internet enabled devices, such as a smartphone or tablet) hard drive or browser, and not on this site.

The cookies used on the Valmet sites may be stored on your device for a longer time or until you manually delete them (stored or persistent cookies) or be deleted from your device after you leave Valmet’s web service (session cookies).

When you visit Valmet’s web sites you may receive cookies from third party websites or domains. We use a number of suppliers that may also set cookies on your device on our behalf to allow them to deliver the services they are providing for Valmet. These cookies include those that collect website usage information about visitors to Valmet's web sites. To get more information about these third party cookies, as well as information about how to opt-out of receiving such cookies, follow the links in the relevant section below.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies and in most browsers you can change your settings to refuse all cookies or to tell you when a cookie is being sent. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about how to adjust or modify your browser settings. Information gathered by cookies is used to improve our communication and is compiled in order to improve the general level of services from Valmet. We cannot identify you personally from this information. Protecting privacy and personal data

Valmet is committed to protecting your privacy and personal data. Valmet applies a high level of protection and processes your personal data in accordance with applicable personal data legislation and privacy principles.

Valmet will only store personal data as required to meet legal and regulatory requirements or as needed to provide better services to you. To provide better services to you it may be necessary to ask for or obtain personal data. If you provide or have provided Valmet with any personal data, Valmet may use it to provide services to you or to respond to your requests. By providing information to Valmet through this site you acknowledge and accept the collection, use and disclosure of personal data of the type and for the limited purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Valmet will not transfer any personal data outside Valmet or its partners and affiliates.

Valmet is continuously developing its websites and may at any time revise the terms of this Privacy Policy by updating it.

### Third party cookies used on Valmet sites

#### Analytics / Tracking Cookies

  * Snoobi web analytics: [More information about how Snoobi works ](http://www.snoobi.fi/)(in Finnish only at the moment)
  * Google Analytics: [More information about how Google Analytics works ](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage)
  * YouTube tracking: [More information (Google service)](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

#### Social media sharing

  * AddThis: [More information on how AddThis works ](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy)
  * Other cookies [More information (Google service)](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)
  * maps.google.com: [More information (Google service)](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)
